<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Bill Zhang</title>
    <link>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Bill Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Middle Fork</title>
      <link>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/post-middlefork/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/post-middlefork/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I made this post originally to try out a gallery feature I was implementing for this website. Coincidentally, I started working on right after I came back from the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.champaignforests.org/forest-preserve/champaign-county/middle-fork-river&#34;&gt;Middle Fork River Forest Preserve&lt;/a&gt;. For some context, Middle Fork is a sectioned out zone in the middle of Illinois (it literally is surrounded on all 4 sides by farm land) that serves as a nature preserve. It also is Illinois&amp;rsquo; only international dark sky park as of 2025. I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to come for a while to take pictures of the stars or milky way, but I never really found the time. Now, on the last few days of spring break, I decided it was worth a trip.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my Webpage!</title>
      <link>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi there! This is the first post on my personal website / blog.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I previously had a personal portfolio website, but I never liked the look of it and it was hard for me to update and add information because I  wrote the whole thing in pure HTML and CSS. 2 years later after I made the intial website, I decided I was going to remake it during spring break, and this is the result!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
